bsnonline.net 2014-07-02

# BSN® - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect, use, and disclose information provided by you while using the Site. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page, so please check this page periodically to ensure that you are informed about any changes that we implement.

## COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. You may be asked to provide your personal information any time you are in contact with us or our affiliates. We may share this personal information with our affiliates and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Here are some examples of the types of personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * When you purchase a product through the Site, we may collect your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card token data, expiration date and billing name and address.
  * The personal information that we collect allows us to keep you posted on our latest product announcements, promotions, special offers, and upcoming events. It also helps us improve our products, services, content, and advertising. If you do not want to be on our electronic mailing list, you can opt out any time. To do so, simply unsubscribe from emails via the unsubscribe link in each email you receive from us.
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications. 
  * We also may use personal information for internal purposes such as audits, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications. 
  * If you enter a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion, we may use the information that you provide to administer those programs. The applicable terms and conditions are independent of this Privacy Policy.

## COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Non-personal information is data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. As is true of most websites, we may store or track non-personal information, such as user Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, and date/time stamp, for any purpose, such as to better understand user behavior and facilitate the effectiveness of our content and advertising. 

## DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

At times, we may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with us to provide products and services, or that help us market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by us to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

We also may disclose any information that we possess about you (including your identity) if we determine that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the Site, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, or the rights or property of visitors to or users of the Site, including our customers. We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information that we deem necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We also may disclose your information when we determine that applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes, or if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms Of Use. Additionally, in the event that we undergo a corporate reorganization, merger, or sale, we may transfer any and all personal information that we collect to any third party involved in such transaction. 

## PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Site; any such transmission is at your own risk. However, we take precautions – including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We will continue to take such precautions for as long as we retain your personal information. 

E-mail Security: "Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, or credit card information. 

## THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SERVICES

The Site may contain links to third-party websites. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or demographic information, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties because we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting third-party websites. 

## COOKIES: DO NOT TRACK REQUESTS

We use cookies and other persistent identifiers to enhance your experience and track information about visitors and visits to our Site. Cookies are small files that enable this Site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser carry certain information. Customer’s may have the ability to have their personal computer warn them each time a cookie is set, or turn off cookies through their browser. Each browser is different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Turning cookies off may interfere with the normal functionality of the site. 

## OPT-OUT, REMOVE OR MODIFY INFORMATION

To modify your e-mail subscription, please unsubscribe from emails via the unsubscribe link in each email. Please note, we maintain information about individual sales transactions in order to service that transaction and for recordkeeping.

Last Updated: March 13, 2014
